Something's off. I don't like this.
The enemy has activated a Stand.
I can feel its presence.
But our enemy isn't in this city.
I can feel it moving farther away.
If it wanted to attack us,
its presence should be
approaching us instead.
What is going on?
There's my body!
The enemy first wants to kill my body,
which is vulnerable without my Stand.
I have to protect my body!
What's this?
Oh! It's Batman!
I found Batman! Awesome!
EPISODE 26: BOHEMIAN ECSTATIC (2)
Shit, why won't my body stay still?
Weather, do you not see me
because you aren't under
the enemy Stand's influence?
Weather, I'm going after my body.
You go hunt down the Stand User!
Anastasia,
where are you?
Scoundrel!
How could you show your face
after what you've done?
I'll call the police right now!
Hello, is this the police?
Wait just a moment.
Were you talking about me?
Stay the hell away from my shop!
Calm down. How about this?
I'm short on time
and I need to speak to you.
The hell that's enough!
You smashed up my tables!
I've got no wife.
I run this place all by myself!
What? So my body came here?
If it's money you want,
just tell me the amount, and I'll pay.
So please, hang up the phone.
Tell me, where did I go?
I need to know.
I mean, that was my twin younger brother.
Is something the matter?
Is there a problem here?
This is Squad 6.
We're following up on a tip
about an escaped convict.
Roger that.
Excuse me, can you turn around?
That's me!
My body is still inside the shop!
Turn around.
Show your face and answer my questions.
It's business as usual,
Officer.
Sorry, you may go.
Wasn't there an old man here?
Diver Drive!
I injected chocolate into my face.
Breaking news.
The famous Japanese character Kenshiro
defeated Raoh the villain
after a showdown in West Shinjuku, Tokyo!
The sequence of events followed
the original works…
Where are you? Show yourself!
- Hurray!
- Princess is awake!
Snow White returned to us!
The chocolate shop owner.
You haven't reached
your happily ever after yet?
I don't need my body anymore!
She's always been in my dreams.
Snow White, my darling!
- And that's how the story goes!
Did they just say "story?"
How could you be so cruel?
How could you
devour my brothers like that?
What is this creature?
I thought that was chocolate
I injected into my face.
Are they goats, or are they chocolate?
"He's a cunning little devil."
"He tricked the seven kids
into opening the door and came inside."
"And then, he cornered the kids
one by one and gobbled them up!"
"The only one that survived
was the youngest kid,
who hid inside the grandfather clock!"
I know this story!
"When the mother goat came home,
she grew very upset!"
"The mother held the scissors
in her cloven hoof,
and went a one, a two at his stomach."
"She took out his guts and
stuffed pebbles in his body."
"Then he got thrown into a pond!"
Don't read such a story!
The villain was a wolf!
The wolf came and ate my brothers!
The enemy Stand wasn't going
after my body.
I was being dragged into
a story!
Excuse me.
Is this the way to
the hospital in Saint-Rémy?
Ask someone else.
Oh? Excuse me.
Wait, I believe you know me.
Sorry, but I can't help you.
I'm not from here.
Never mind that.
Aren't you my fan?
I can tell from your face.
You've been inspired by me.
My name
is Van Gogh.
I am Van Gogh's self-portrait.
Yesterday, I cut off my ear with a razor.
See, you were moved by me again.
Mommy's coming back with scissors!
Our mommy's going to get you!
Bad wolf!
Bring it, fucker!
Mommy! We're over here!
We're trapped in here!
What the hell?
Save us!
How dare you!
How could you eat my babies?
Continuing report
on the fantasy hero incident.
The incident is believed to have
started in Florida, USA, a few hours ago.
Not only are cartoon
and story characters brought to life,
but even figures from artworks
are being sighted.
The riches of all humanity,
the treasures for our souls
are vanishing!
This User doesn't care about
causing chaos around the world.
Their only objective
is to keep the priest safe.
The Stand itself is invincible.
The only way to win is to strike the User!
The User is headed north. I can sense it.
It's moving at a pretty fast pace.
It's getting farther away from here!
Here's a question.
How many self-portraits did I paint,
before my untimely death?
Back off, or I'll kick you!
The answer is about 40.
Van Gogh left that many self-portraits.
It was before I cut off an ear.
Then I ended my 37 years of life,
killing myself with a gun!
I see you are one of my self-portraits.
Hello, Van Gogh with a severed ear.
What?
Van Gogh shot himself in the head twice.
A single bullet wasn't enough
to end his life.
That's right. He needed to shoot himself
twice to seal the deal.
This enemy!
Weather Forecast!
Direction is north.
Shut down the highway with a rainstorm,
up to 30 kilometers north!
Don't let a single car head north!
Diver Drive restructured the door
from the inside.
It's been fused with the wall.
Nothing can open this door now!
Diver Drive!
My brothers are free!
And that's how the story goes!
Once a story begins,
nothing can alter its course.
I'm powerless against this Stand!
The walls, Diver Drive!
Submerge!
Hell yes, I'm safe.
Officers from earlier.
So their souls have also split
from their bodies.
Anyhow, I'm taking this police car…
- Pebbles! Get the pebbles!
- Mommy!
I can't escape.
Weather, hurry and kill the User!
I sensed the enemy up north,
but now it's down south.
No way…
Is it in the air?
Flight 8250, destination Key West.
Despite the sudden downpour,
we were able to depart on time.
This ability that recently awakened
within me.
I can only be defeated if
I'm in direct harm's way
Nothing can touch me when
I'm high up in the air.
I'm finally living my life to the fullest.
This power keeps my blood racing.
THE NIGHT BEFORE
To be born
means to be chosen.
Once one is chosen,
one is protected and supported by all.
Amidst the competitions of life,
the chosen one rises above.
Those who were drawn to me.
They exist to bring me to heaven
when the rightful time arrives.
Yes, Jolyne Cujoh may have escaped
to chase me down,
but she merely exists
to help me attain heaven.
Sons of Dio,
help me get to Cape Canaveral.
This act will be
your singular source of joy.
All my life,
I felt like a tumbling rock
that rolls without a purpose.
But now I understand.
I was born to use my ability!
I'll do whatever it takes
to protect the priest.
Also, Bohemian Ecstatic is magnificent!
It makes me laugh to watch
society fall into utter darkness.
The very society that despised me!
No, I can't catch up.
If the Stand User is on an airplane,
its speed exceeds 400kph.
Even the largest hurricane on record
cannot travel faster than 280kph.
There's not a single weather phenomenon
that can catch up to an airplane.
It got away!
One more bullet.
If I take one more bullet,
this story will end.
Dammit!
Don't you dare get close to that gun.
If you touch it, I'll kill you!
Anastasia!
Weather.
What?
Weather!
Yes! The wolf is drowned!
- And that's how the story goes!
- Hurray!
It's over. That's how the end goes.
I'll live a happy life in your place.
According to the experts,
the city with the most damage
due to the fantasy hero incident…
What is your wish, Aladdin?
I am your loyal servant.
- I can grant any wish.
- Shut up, brat!
What are you reading? Let me see.
I can't breathe!
You want me to do more?
No, this is fine. Thanks.
You've got real talent.
What's with the drawing, Weather?
I got this Van Gogh to draw,
and create a new character.
He comes with a story of his own.
This hero can use an ability.
It sucks all the fantasy heroes
back into their stories!
This hero's story will end
once its ability restores order
to our reality!
We're going back,
and that's how the story goes.
We will now rejoin our unharmed bodies!
Hey, are you listening?
Can I have my book back?
Breaking news.
Order has been restored.
Characters from story books,
cartoons, movies, and artwork
are back where they belong.
This includes Mona Lisa, Snow White,
Batman, and Tweety.
However, for some unknown reason,
Pinocchio is still missing.
Did you fall asleep?
Was it too boring?
But this story is full
of hopes and dreams.
UNGALO
STAND NAME: BOHEMIAN ECSTATIC
BACK TO DESPAIR
BEYOND RECOVERY
Hey, what do you drive now?
I hope
you got rid of that one, Romeo.
Jolyne!
Please. Help me, Jolyne!
- Do you know what a "plea deal" is?
- …you will be sent to Green Dolphin…
Romeo!
You…
How did you…
Let me warn you, Romeo.
Stay away from the phone.
All phones.
Got that?
That's the last thing on my mind.
Ever since that day, I've felt so sorry.
I realized my own foolishness
only after I lost you.
Oh, god.
How can I ever make up
for what I've done to you--
There's no need for words, Romeo.
You are the best I ever had.
I need you.
I tried to go visit you,
but they wouldn't let me.
Romeo, you poor boy.
I really pity you.
Nothing matters anymore
about the hit-and-run.
I have nothing against you.
After all, you got embroiled
in a conspiracy.
Romeo, I came to ask you for a favor.
I need money and a car.
I have to go somewhere.
I only have a thousand dollars on me.
Take these keys.
This is plenty. Thank you, Romeo.
Just don't talk if the police come.
Promise me.
Oh, Jolyne,
I will confess my crimes.
I'll get you a non-guilty verdict.
So please, come back to me!
Wow, car keys!
Hello? I'm Romeo Jisso,
a Palm Beach resident.
Is this the police?
I'm reporting an escaped convict.
Yes, it's Jolyne Cujoh.
I knew it.
It was wise that you used my sticker
to make a copy of his tongue.
This asshole is already ratting you out.
No, she didn't!
She didn't come to my house.
Why would she?
I'm filing a report because she called.
Yes, we only talked over the phone.
She asked for money
but I didn't give her any.
She said she's headed to Mexico.
Of course, I will make another call
if she contacts me again.
Yes. Bye.
I'm impressed.
He kept his word.
I will do anything for her.
Anything to atone for my actions.
Jolyne!
Wow, your ex-boyfriend is awesome!
Guess what the key is for?
He gave us car keys too, but guess what?
Look over there!
Can we ride it?
I want to try piloting it.
I bet it's totally different
from reading about it in a book!
Romeo, I stand corrected.
But let's rip this off. For good measure.
Let's get going.
The helicopter will get us there
in a matter of hours.
Father,
I understand my assignment to protect you.
Can you do something
about my eyelid first?
One of my eyelids
always slides down for no reason.
I can't open my eye.
I mean, I can get it to open sometimes.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter